<messages>
    <chat>Say something in chat! Don't be shy</chat>
    <chat>Cannibals don't eat clowns because they taste funny.</chat>
    <chat>If all the world's a stage, where does the audience sit?</chat>
    <chat>If one synchronized swimmer drowns, do the others drown too? Creepy.</chat>
    <chat>Why did Yankee Doodle name the feather in his hat Macaroni? Answer in chat.</chat>
    <chat>If electricity comes from electrons, does morality comes from morons?</chat>
    <chat>Why does someone believe you when you say there are four billion stars, but check when you say the paint is wet?</chat>
    <chat>What if Batman gets bitten by a vampire?</chat>
    <chat>Can we spell creativity however we want?</chat>
    <chat>What was the greatest thing BEFORE sliced bread?</chat>
    <chat>Why isn't chocolate considered a vegetable, if chocolate comes from cocoa beans,  and all beans are a vegetable?</chat>
    <chat>Do pyromaniacs wear blazers? Answer in chat.</chat>
    <chat>Blurt out a line from a favorite song.</chat>
    <chat>What is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow?</chat>
    <chat>Eat a live toad the first thing in the morning and nothing worse will happen to you the rest of the day.</chat>
    <chat>Nothing is as simple as we hope it will be. - Jim Horning</chat>
    <chat>An inconvenience is an adventure wrongly considered. G. K. Chesterton</chat>
    <chat>As pretty as an Airport.</chat>
    <chat>Automatic simply means that you cannot repair it yourself.</chat>
    <chat>A Smith &amp; Wesson always beats four aces.</chat>
    <chat>A bird in hand is safer than one overhead.</chat>
    <chat>A bird in the hand is worth about three Kleenex.</chat>
    <chat>A closed mouth says nothing wrong; a closed mind does nothing right.</chat>
    <chat>A computer makes as many mistakes in one second as three men working  for thirty years straight.</chat>
    <chat>A dog is a dog except when he is facing you. Then he is Mr. Dog.</chat>
    <chat>A fellow who is always declaring that he is no fool usually harbors suspicions to the contrary.</chat>
    <chat>A fool and his money are some party.</chat>
    <chat>A hunch is creativity trying to tell you something.</chat>
    <chat>A major failure will not occur until after this game has passed final exhaustive teting.</chat>
    <chat>A minecrafter builds castles in the air. A psychotic lives in castles in the air. And a psychiatrist is the guy who collects the rent.</chat>
    <chat>Lovely weather we are having within the game, don't you think?</chat>
    <chat>A synonym is a word you use when you can't spell the other one.</chat>
    <chat>Minecraft rivalries are so intense because the stakes are so small.</chat>
    <chat>All things are possible. Except skiing through a revolving door.</chat>
    <chat>All turtle thoughts are of turtle.</chat>
    <chat>All warranties expire upon payment of invoice.</chat>
    <chat>Almost everything in life is easier to get into than out of.</chat>
    <chat>Always address your elders with respect; they could leave you a fortune.</chat>
    <chat>Forgive your enemies - nothing else annoys them as much.</chat>
    <chat>An elephant is a mouse built to government specifications.</chat>
    <chat>An expert is one who knows more and more about less and less until he knows absolutely everything about nothing.</chat>
    <chat>Be nice to your team. An unhappy crew makes for a dangerous voyage.</chat>
    <chat>Any given computer program, when running, is obsolete.</chat>
    <chat>Bad weather forecasts are more often right than good ones.</chat>
    <chat>Black holes are outa sight!</chat>
    <chat>Blessed are the censors, for they shall inhibit the earth. (Cool chat filter, huh?)</chat>
    <chat>Computers are unreliable, but humans are even more unreliable.</chat>
    <chat>Confidence is the feeling you had before you knew better.</chat>
    <chat>Did you know that if you maintain a cholesterol-free diet, your body makes its own cholesterol?</chat>
    <chat>Don't wear earmuffs in a bed of rattlesnakes.</chat>
    <chat>Every calling is great when greatly pursued.</chat>
    <chat>Every family tree has some sap.</chat>
    <chat>Everyone has a scheme for getting rich that will not work.</chat>
    <chat>Everything comes to he who waits. You just need infinite patience.</chat>
    <chat>Show someone your gratitude today.</chat>
    <chat>We are really glad you are playing this game today.</chat>
    <chat>Get up and stretch once in awhile.</chat>
    <chat>Time to stop playing and get outside?</chat>
    <chat>Say something nice to another player.</chat>
    <chat>How much does it cost to ride a PCI bus? 2 Bits.</chat>
    <chat>Designed with you in mind by people who have in mind what you should have in mind.</chat>
    <chat>Secrecy is the beginning of tyranny.</chat>
    <chat>If the only tool you have is a hammer, all problems will look like nails</chat>
    <chat>Don't try to have the last word. You might get it.</chat>
    <chat>Never throw an egg at an electric fan.</chat>
    <chat>Reading is thinking with someone else's head instead of one's own.</chat>
    <chat>Disclose classified information only when a NEED TO KNOW exists.</chat>
    <chat>Acquaintance: a person whom we know well enough to borrow from, but not well enough to lend to.</chat>
    <chat>To laugh at men of sense is the privilege of fools.</chat>
    <chat>Let a fool hold his tongue and he will pass for a sage.</chat>
    <chat>What kind of sound does a sub-atomic duck make? Quark!!</chat>
    <chat>You can pay for a capacitor with cash but it is better to charge it.</chat>
    <chat>Today is a good day to count your blessings</chat>
    <chat>Let not the sands of time get in your lunch.</chat>
    <chat>Never play leap frog with a unicorn.</chat>
    <chat>He who laughs, lasts</chat>
    <chat>Make trades with other players</chat>
    <chat>The game is more fun when you are on a team</chat>
    <chat>An asylum for the sane would be empty.</chat>
    <chat>Call a friend IRL today.</chat>
    <chat>May you live all the days of your life.</chat>
    <chat>Speak well of your friends</chat>
    <chat>Did you hear the one about the athelete who was so proud of his gold medal that he had it bronzed?</chat>
    <chat>Work expands to fill the time available for its completion.</chat>
    <chat>The junk you have will expand to fill the available space.</chat>
    <chat>THE PETER PRINCIPLE: In every hierarchy, each employee tends to rise to  his level of incompetence.</chat>
    <chat>CHEOPS' LAW: Nothing ever gets built on schedule or within budget.</chat>
    <chat>MURPHY'S LAW: If something can go wrong, it will.</chat>
    <chat>WEILER'S LAW: Nothing is impossible for the man who does not have to do it himself.</chat>
    <chat>When all else fails, read the instructions.</chat>
    <chat>We are thinking of rewriting this in FORTRAN (Ask your parents what that is)</chat>
    <chat>Government intervention in the free market always leads to a lower national standard of living.</chat>
    <chat>It is much harder to find a friend than to keep one.</chat>
    <chat>Established technology tends to persist in spite of new    technology.</chat>
    <chat>Adding manpower to a late software project makes it later.</chat>
    <chat>People occasionally stumble over the truth but most of the time pick themselves up and continue on as if nothing had happened.</chat>
    <chat>Cole's Law: Thinly sliced cabbage.</chat>
    <chat>There ain't no such thing as a free lunch.</chat>
    <chat>The other line moves faster.</chat>
    <chat>Whenever possible blame the hardware.</chat>
    <chat>Every person has a scheme that will not work.</chat>
    <chat>In order to get a loan you must first prove you don't need it.</chat>
    <chat>Save 10 percent of your income.</chat>
    <chat>Friends may come and go, but enemies accumulate.</chat>
    <chat>Law of Selective Gravity   (The Buttered Side Down Law) An object will fall so as to do the most damage.</chat>
    <chat>You cannot successfully determine beforehand which side of the bread to butter.</chat>
    <chat>Fancy gizmos seldom work.</chat>
    <chat>Pereto's principle: 80 percent of the production comes from 20 percent of the producers</chat>
    <chat>you can't tell how deep a puddle is until you step into it.</chat>
    <chat>Nothing is as easy as it looks.</chat>
    <chat>Everything takes longer than you think.</chat>
    <chat>It is impossible to make anything foolproof because fools are so ingenious.</chat>
    <chat>A bird in the hand is safer than one overhead.</chat>
    <chat>Variables won't, constants aren't.</chat>
    <chat>Expenditures rise to meet income.</chat>
    <chat>Live within your means. (VIP is very affordable!)</chat>
    <chat>Everyone has good qualities</chat>
    <chat>It works better if you plug it in.</chat>
    <chat>A man with one watch knows what time it is; a man with two watches is never sure.</chat>
    <chat>The intensity of movie publicity is in inverse ratio to the quality of the movie.</chat>
    <chat>There is no direct relationship between the quality of an educational program and its cost.</chat>
    <chat>If you want a track team to win the high jump you find one person who can jump seven feet, not seven people who can jump one foot.</chat>
    <chat>If you cannot convince them, confuse them.</chat>
    <chat>The easiest way of making money is to stop losing it.</chat>
    <chat>Industry always moves in to fill an economic vacuum.</chat>
    <chat>The sooner and in more detail you announce bad news, the better.</chat>
    <chat>He who hesitates is lost.</chat>
    <chat>When in Rome, do as the Romans do.</chat>
    <chat>It is never too late to learn.</chat>
    <chat>You can't teach an old dog new tricks. It's illegal.</chat>
    <chat>Act in haste, repent at leisure. (Look before you leap.)</chat>
    <chat>Out of sight, out of mind.</chat>
    <chat>Absence makes the heart grow fonder.</chat>
    <chat>Many hands make light work.</chat>
    <chat>Actions speak louder than words.</chat>
    <chat>Never change horses in mid-stream.</chat>
    <chat>Silence is golden. (So why do we keep putting out these messages?)</chat>
    <chat>The squeaky wheel gets the grease.</chat>
    <chat>Practice makes perfect.</chat>
    <chat>All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy.</chat>
    <chat>A penny saved is a penny earned.</chat>
    <chat>It's much easier to ride a horse the way he is going.</chat>
    <chat>Never try to outstubborn a cat</chat>
    <chat>Please engage brain before setting mouth into motion.</chat>
    <chat>One man's bug is another man's feature</chat>
    <chat>"MEOW"...SPLAT..."RUFF"...SPLAT...(Raining cats &amp; dogs)</chat>
    <chat>WHO CARES where Carmen Sandiego is?</chat>
    <chat>(A)bort, (R)etry, (F)ail, (G)rab_Hammer</chat>
    <chat>A field upgrade, HAL. We're going to make you IBM compatible.</chat>
    <chat>A nudist has no reason to fear a pickpocket.</chat>
    <chat>Smile.  It makes people wonder what you're up to.</chat>
    <chat>copy *.txt > brain</chat>
    <chat>Cross river THEN insult alligator.</chat>
    <chat>Despite the high cost of living, it remains popular.</chat>
    <chat>Did you expect mere proof to sway my opinion</chat>
    <chat>Do radioactive cats have eighteen half-lives?</chat>
    <chat>Do witches use Spell-checkers?</chat>
    <chat>Pirate software comes with a treasure map.</chat>
    <chat>Don't lend people money.  It causes amnesia.</chat>
    <chat>Don't look now, but your file is unzipped.</chat>
    <chat>Don't worry the next message will be better!</chat>
    <chat>Error-Disk Full Error,Formatting Drive C: to make space Just kidding!</chat>
    <chat>Everyone is gifted. Some just open their packages sooner.</chat>
    <chat>Help stamp out, eliminate, and abolish redundancy!</chat>
    <chat>Hire teenagers while they still know everything.</chat>
    <chat>Hong Kong, Son of King Kong</chat>
    <chat>Hot water Heaters: hot water needs heating?</chat>
    <chat>I can keep a secret.  It's the people I tell that can't</chat>
    <chat>I can SPELL, I just can't TYPE worth a hoot !</chat>
    <chat>I got everything but the part after "Now listen closely".</chat>
    <chat>I haven't lost my mind, it's backed up on disk</chat>
    <chat>I was so much older then, I'm younger than that now</chat>
    <chat>Observe National Apathy Week.</chat>
    <chat>Teach your cat to yodel</chat>
    <chat>If at first you don't succeed, call it Beta</chat>
    <chat>If corn oil comes from corn, where does baby oil . . .</chat>
    <chat>If I save time, when do I get it back ?</chat>
    <chat>If I throw a cat out the car window, is it kitty litter?</chat>
    <chat>Join in on chats, they are fun</chat>
    <chat>Junk - stuff we throw away.  Stuff - junk we keep.</chat>
    <chat>Luxuriantly hand-crafted from only the finest ASCII.</chat>
    <chat>Microwave Hint#3: Make a hole in the turtle's shell first</chat>
    <chat>Never fight with a bear in his own cave.</chat>
    <chat>No Credit, Bad Credit? No Problem. No Money?  Problem.</chat>
    <chat>Thank-you for helping us grow the network.</chat>
    <chat>Speak kindly to one another.</chat>
    <chat>Programmers don't get sniffles, they get a CODE.</chat>
    <chat>Proofread carefully to see if you any words out!</chat>
    <chat>Public Restroom-The only place a flush beats a full house</chat>
    <chat>Purranoia: the fear one's cats are up to something.</chat>
    <chat>Santa's elves are just a bunch of subordinate Clauses.</chat>
    <chat>Some days you're the windshield, some days the bug.</chat>
    <chat>The tuna doesn't taste the same without the dolphin.</chat>
    <chat>The wise open their minds, but a fool opens his mouth.</chat>
    <chat>To err is human, to forgive is against my policy</chat>
    <chat>To err is human. To moo is bovine.</chat>
    <chat>We'll burn that bridge when we come to it.</chat>
    <chat>We're lost but we're making good time.</chat>
    <chat>Well, to be frank, I'd have to change my name.</chat>
    <chat>What are the instructions doing in the trash?</chat>
    <chat>What if there were no hypothetical questions?</chat>
    <chat>What was the best thing BEFORE sliced bread?</chat>
    <chat>When a cow laughs, does milk come up its nose?</chat>
    <chat>You are in a maze of twisty little programs, all alike.</chat>
    <chat>You may use this opinion for a two week trial period.</chat>
    <chat>You used to be indecisive.  Now you're not sure.</chat>
    <chat>You will become rich and famous unless you don't.</chat>
    <chat>A wise son brings joy to his father.</chat>
    <chat>The wise in heart accept commands.</chat>
    <chat>Whoever takes crooked paths will be found out.</chat>
    <chat>Love covers over all wrongs.</chat>
    <chat>With humility comes wisdom.</chat>
    <chat>Hopes placed in mortals die with them.</chat>
    <chat>A gossip betrays a confidence, but a trustworthy person keeps a secret.</chat>
    <chat>You will never be younger then you are today.</chat>
</messages>
